[
  {
    "question": "How much of the earth land surface rainforests cover?",
    "optionOne": "4%.",
    "optionTwo": "12%.",
    "optionThree": "21%.",
    "correctAnswer": "12%."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does equable mean?",
    "optionOne": "With the same amount.",
    "optionTwo": "With not much variation.",
    "optionThree": "Within the equator.",
    "correctAnswer": "With not much variation."
  },
  {
    "question": "How many layers structure the the jungle?",
    "optionOne": "4.",
    "optionTwo": "6.",
    "optionThree": "8.",
    "correctAnswer": "4."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why the vegetation of the understory layer develops large leaves?",
    "optionOne": "To catch as much water as possible.",
    "optionTwo": "To host a specific parasite.",
    "optionThree": "To catch the remaining sunlight.",
    "correctAnswer": "To catch the remaining sunlight."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is buttress roots?",
    "optionOne": "An animal only living in tree's roots.",
    "optionTwo": "Shallow and widespread roots structure.",
    "optionThree": "A name given to very soft roots.",
    "correctAnswer": "Shallow and widespread roots structure."
  },
  {
    "question": "What characterize the Canopy?",
    "optionOne": "Dense vegetation with a huge network of branches and leaves.",
    "optionTwo": "Light vegetation with definite and seperated zones.",
    "optionThree": "Dark and humide where vegetation has difficulty to grow.",
    "correctAnswer": "Dense vegetation with a huge network of branches and leaves."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why trees develop buttress roots?",
    "optionOne": "To prevent other trees to grow.",
    "optionTwo": "To catch as much sunlight as possible.",
    "optionThree": "Because the humus layer is very thin.",
    "correctAnswer": "Because the humus layer is very thin."
  },
  {
    "question": "How hight can reach the Emergent layer?",
    "optionOne": "60 meters.",
    "optionTwo": "100 meters.",
    "optionThree": "120 meters.",
    "correctAnswer": "60 meters."
  },
  {
    "question": "What part of the animals population live in the canopy?",
    "optionOne": "About 21%.",
    "optionTwo": "About 50%.",
    "optionThree": "About 90%.",
    "correctAnswer": "About 50%."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is biology?",
    "optionOne": "The science of organism living in pairs.",
    "optionTwo": "The science of life and living organisms.",
    "optionThree": "The person that study the Earth.",
    "correctAnswer": "The science of life and living organisms."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the largest rainforest?",
    "optionOne": "The Amazon.",
    "optionTwo": "The Daintree.",
    "optionThree": "The Congo.",
    "correctAnswer": "The Amazon."
  },
  {
    "question": "About 25% of what comes from the Jungle?",
    "optionOne": "Medicines.",
    "optionTwo": "Wood.",
    "optionThree": "Water.",
    "correctAnswer": "Medicines."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is humus?",
    "optionOne": "The decay of the forest elements.",
    "optionTwo": "A species of frog.",
    "optionThree": "The name a flower that only Grows in the jungle.",
    "correctAnswer": "The decay of the forest elements."
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is situated the Amazon?",
    "optionOne": "South Africa.",
    "optionTwo": "South America.",
    "optionThree": "Australia.",
    "correctAnswer": "South America."
  }
]